Sviatoslav

Pidhurskyi



Contact

Phone:

+380 96 77 84 404

Email:

svyatddev@gmail.com

Links:

- broodd.vercel.app
- GitHub

Languages

Ukrainian - Native

English – between A2 – B1

Russian - Proficiency

Hobbies

- Skiing
- Photography
- Developing cool stuff
- Riding my bike on the road

Summary

Hi there, I Full Stack Developer which started work in developing since 2017.

Always was interesting into update my level so sometimes created hobby projects for learn new stack technologies, improve in code writing and architecture in general. (Can see hobby projects in **portfolio**)

Interested in professional growth and the study of new technologies with cool team & get fun with it.

Technologies

Back-end

- Node.js (Nest.js, Express.js)
- Databases (PostgreSQL, SQL, MongoDB)
- ORMs (Sequelize, TypeORM)

Front-end

React.js / Vue.js

Mobile apps

- Ionic
- NativeScript

Other

- WordPress
- TypeScript
- Telegraf.js (Telegram bots)

Experience

Back-end Developer - 08/2020 to 01/2021 IT IS.TEAM, contract & remote

- Worked with cool team for develop social-event app.
- Worked with a team of 10 people, developers, QA, PM and kanban masters.
- Organization of process was based on kanban.
- Built CI/CD pipelines using GitLab, Docker and custom scripts - helping deploy.
- Develop REST API Nest.js server.
- Used external services like Firebase and others for implement user authorization, push notifications & email notifications.
- System and database architecture development.

Full stack / WP Developer - 05/2019 to 02/2020 **Developer**, full time

- Implement REST API server with microservices and payment of site services using Node.js.
- Designed and constructed web user interfaces and visual elements using Vue.js.
- Developed full functionality dynamic and interactive websites using WordPress & frameworks.

Front-end / WP Developer - 08/2017 to 04/2019 FlyFox, remote

- Developed full functionality dynamic and interactive websites using WordPress & frameworks.
- Fixed bugs from existing websites and performance.

Education

Software Engineering - 2019/2022

Bachelor of Science in Software Development Ivano-Frankivsk National Technical University of Oil and Gas

Software Engineering - 2015/2019

College of Electronic Devices Ivano-Frankivsk National Technical University of Oil and Gas